One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Cross this endless sea with me and search for
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please, following
the footprints of those who pursue their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we put our minds together,
we'll get through it
always
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Keep chasing, keep chasing
the compass that leads to our dreams
always points straight ahead
We can't stop here
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can take hold of tomorrow
Keep chasing, keep chasing
everything we see in the moment,
we should record it all
in the blank slates of our minds
The Terrifying Emergency Broadcast
I'm impressed. I'll give you that much.
It's hard to believe that you've come this far... all by yourself.
There's no way I could come this far by myself,
and I wouldn't even wanna come by myself.
Unlike you guys, I don't work alone!
Soon all my friends will be here!
Tempest Kick!
Shave!
Th-Th-That was close!
Don't let your guard down!
O-Okay.
And don't do anything stupid!
Hm?! What's that supposed
to mean?! How insulting!
You're so damn rude!
Oh no! It's so slippery that I can't stand.
Even still,
just you wait. I'm about to get you back!
Ow, ow, ow. That damn deer-gorilla!
How dare he humiliate me?!
But the key is more important! We gotta get the key!
I'd better hurry to that secretary woman.
Deer-gorilla! Wait, you jerk!
Let's go, Oimo!
Yeah, Kashi!
We've got to try and take them out one at a time!
Artillery squad! Concentrate
your fire on Kashi's feet!
Now! Charge!
Has the situation outside changed?
The giants who changed sides have been doing all they can to defend us,
but I guess they're at the end of their rope.
Hey! Hey, hurry up!
Dammit! What a disaster.
I can't believe a pirate could get this far.
Hey, everyone, come in!
CP9! What the hell are you all doing?!
A pirate has made it nearly to the bridge!
Hey, are you listening?! Say something!
Wait!
You're holding...
Whaaat?!
The... The... The golden transponder snail!
Navy
The silver transponder snail
has received a signal!
A buster call has been sounded!
Admiral Aokiji has sounded a buster call!
Where?
Enies Lobby!
Have the five vice admirals closest to the target respond!
Considering the distance,
I think it's quicker to head
there from headquarters.
How long will it take?
It's possible to get there within 30 minutes.
Immediately have ten battleships
get ready to set sail,
and summon five vice admirals!
Double time!
Yes, sir!
A buster call has been sounded!
The target is Enies Lobby!
Have ten battleships get
ready to set sail immediately!
Hey! Hey!
Yes, Chief.
Dammit! Oh, crap! This one is
the mobile transponder snail.
What have I done? I wasn't careful.
How did I press the button
on the golden transponder snail?!
How could I have...
sounded a buster call?!
A-a buster call? I-It can't be!
What's this? Some announcement?
How could you do something so stupid?! Rescind the order immediately!
That's Robin's voice!
It'll be a disaster!
Robin!
What? "Rescind the order"?
Hey, hey. Who do you think you're talking to?
What the heck is this broadcast?
Hey! Don't move!
We can't move!
A buster call is a great idea!
What's wrong with it?!
That's Chief Spandam's voice, right?
That's right. There's no problem.
I'm the chief of Cipher Pol No. 9.
To facilitate handing you over to the government,
I sounded a buster call.
I see no problem in that!
Even in the worst-case scenario,
we'll be sure to put an end to those pirates.
How could you be so absurd?!
I thought I told you!
That won't be the end of it!
There's no humanity in that attack!
That's the chief, but who's the woman?
The attack will burn
Enies Lobby to the ground!
Buildings, people... the very island itself!
It's a nightmarish concentration of fire that
sacrifices everything to achieve its goal!
That's the buster call!
You have no idea what happened on Ohara twenty years ago!
That's fine. It means that this is
very important to the government.
Now that that idiot Cutty Flam has
burned the blueprints for Pluton,
your existence is the only
clue to the ancient weapon.
A military power that can turn this
whole era upside down is at stake.
If it improves our chances of killing
those idiots trying to get you back,
even if it causes the death
of thousands of soldiers,
we can say that it's an unavoidable
sacrifice for our glorious future!
Above all of that, my promotion is at stake, too.
What?! What's he saying?!
He's gonna sacrifice us?! You gotta be kidding!
What do you think of people's lives?!
Don't forget that CP9 is the
government's secret organization.
If we need 100 deaths in
order to save 1,000 lives,
we won't hesitate to take those 100 lives on the spot.
Mercilessness is also
a necessity for true justice.
Besides, those incompetent soldiers
who couldn't stop the invading pirates...
are better off dead, you idiot!
That mobile transponder snail is transmitting.
What?
Ahhh! Shoot!
Did everyone hear what I just said?!
S-So... my name is Straw Hat Luffy.
You liar!
Everyone! Leave the island!
Enies Lobby is the target of a buster call!
If you stay on the island, you won't survive!
This isn't your concern!
– A b-...
– A buster call...
It sounds like a buster call has been sounded.
What the hell is that man doing?
Sounds like there's some sort of danger.
It's me who's in danger!
I feel sorry for you guys.
Now you have no hope.
Don't worry.
We're used to situations like this.
Pirate kid, what kind of
star were you born under?
This is getting even more interesting!
A buster call has been sounded!
Battleships are coming!
Get off of Enies Lobby!
Battleships are coming? Why are
the Navy soldiers running away?
The woman said that the island
will be burned to the ground.
But this is the government's island!
How should I know why?!
Hey, hey! If you guys are running away,
at least untie us first!
It's a buster call!
We'll be dead if we stay here!
Bring some ships to the front!
Get ready to sail!
The Navy is coming to attack!
We got left behind.
Hey! What're we gonna do?!
Isn't this dangerous?!
It's been dangerous ever since
we set foot in this place.
What about our bro?! What's gonna
happen to Big Bro Franky?!
Yeah. If he doesn't make it back here,
we can't go home together!
The Straw Hats, too!
So what about us?!
What will... happen to all of us?!
We can't afford to waste time, either.
Yeah, we have to take them out quickly
and hurry to the Gates of Justice.
I've got an idea.
Wh-What? What idea?
A way to get the handcuffs off?
Or a way to escape from here?
You are the named blade Nose Storm.
This is no time to give me a nice name!
Chopper! What's taking so long?!
How dare you open your mouth
and say something so stupid?!
If the pirates really get away,
how are you going to...
take responsibility for it?!
What was that?!
Where was Robin speaking from?!
The other side of these doors.
I can't let you pass.
At least give me time to say that.
Get out of my way.
Robin's behind those doors, right?!
Yeah, she's there. So what?
You won't be able to see her...
ever again.
The pressure sure has suddenly ramped up.
Sounds like if I stay in this tower for too long, I may die.
If you're gonna run, then leave the key here.
Shave!
I'm sorry.
I wanted to spend more time playing with you.
Shoot!
We have to quickly evacuate, too.
Golden Bubbles!
This is the same attack that got Sanji-kun.
I thought I was being careful.
I can't hold my Clima-Tact.
My entire body is slippery! I can't stand up!
How dare you make my body like this?!
Although it has the downside
of reducing your curves,
it does give you the most beautiful skin.
I envy you.
But in return, your fighting
ability is reduced by half.
You should just give up on the key I have.
I... I can't do that!
Cool Charge!
That's no use. Playtime is over.
Tempest Kick!
What?
Mirage Tempo.
I'm right here.
When did you...?! What's going on?
Finger Pistol!
Another fake! Where are you this time?!
This way! Right here!
What's that?!
Sh-She became huge?!
What?
So you have powers, too?
She's a ditz.
Robin!
It's a buster call!
Battleships are coming!
Hurry, or we'll be burned to a crisp!
Get out of here!
Zoan type? So is that your trump card?!
Seriously, that's not me!
At the same time, that thing...
It looks like a reindeer, and I know that
hat and the mark on it without a doubt.
But I can't believe...
this is Chopper!
What savage beast's power does she hold?!
Moon Walk!
Tempest Kick!
Hey! Stop it!
What?!
Chopper! Hey, you're Chopper, right?
How did you become like that?!
I guess he can't recognize me
since I look like this.
Aren't you Chopper?!
Let me tell you something!
I didn't think that was you!
Chopper!
Sh-She ignored me! How insolent!
Chopper! What's wrong?!
Take a good look at me! It's me! I'm Nami!
Chopper!
Chopper! Stop it!
Sanji-kun is downstairs!
Where did such a monster stray in here from?
Don't hurt him! He's my friend!
What happened to Chopper?
This is terrible. I have to stop him right away.
That's your friend? You pirates
sure own a creepy pet, huh?
Chopper!
She ignored me again! How insolent!
You're free to go stop that monster,
but I have a duty to stop you, too.
I'm gonna hurry up and finish it here.
Tempest Kick!
This is bad! Even the soles
are slippery. I can't dodge it!
Huh?! I dodged it!
Ah... My right leg returned to normal.
Why? What caused it?
It's wet.
It got wet in all that commotion. Oh, that's right!
Water! I can wash off
the soap power with water!
Aren't you being too optimistic?
Even if you figured out how
to undo Golden Bubbles,
there's no way I'd let you do that.
Sheep Cloud: Relaxing Bubbles!
I'll blow away those bubbles with wind!
Cyclone...
Shoot!
O... Oh, no... My strength is...
Elastic Finger Pistol...
Tact...
Whip!
That was helpful.
Helpful?
If you toss me around like that,
the annoying bubbles on my
body get tossed off, too.
You're bluffing. If you so wish,
I'll keep throwing you around until you die.
The forecast is cloudy!
Cloudy Tempo!
This is different from the
magic show stuff I used to do!
Clouds? More lightning?
Thunder doesn't get generated
from such thin clouds.
Instead, they'll condense!
Don't tell me!
No, she might do it!
The forecast is rain!
Cool Ball!
Shave!
Pour down!
Rain Tempo!
You're not sweet at all. After I was nice
enough to make your skin silky smooth.
If being sweet means not
putting up a fight, then I'll pass.
Cool Charge!
What?
Mirage Tempo!
She disappeared?!
Now I understand your powers,
as well as the strength of CP9.
What's this?!
Mirage Tempo:
Fata Morgana!